{"id_chain": [1], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3}, "problem": "A robe takes 2 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.  How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?", "solutions": [3]}
{"id_chain": [48], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8}, "problem": "Tracy used a piece of wire 4 feet long to support tomato plants in the garden. The wire that Tracy used was cut into pieces 6 inches long. How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?", "solutions": [8]}
{"id_chain": [4], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20}, "problem": "Every day, Wendi feeds each of her chickens three cups of mixed chicken feed, containing seeds, mealworms and vegetables to help keep them healthy. Wendi gives her chickens their feed in three separate meals. In the morning, Wendi gives her flock of chickens 15 cups of feed.  In the afternoon, Wendi gives her chickens another 25 cups of feed. The size of Wendi's flock is 20 chickens. How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?", "solutions": [20]}
{"id_chain": [69], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much money did Bailey start with?": 60}, "problem": "Bailey starts with a certain amount of money. Bailey receives a weekly allowance of $5 for 8 weeks. At the end of 8 weeks, Bailey has a total of $100. How much money did Bailey start with?", "solutions": [60]}
{"id_chain": [50], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294}, "problem": "Lloyd has an egg farm. Lloyd's chickens produce 252 eggs per day and he sells them for $2 per dozen.  How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?", "solutions": [294]}
{"id_chain": [73], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255}, "problem": "Shiela bought five cell phones for $150 each for a 3-month installment. A 2% interest will be charged for each cell phone Shiela buys. How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?", "solutions": [255]}
{"id_chain": [86], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22}, "problem": "Greg has an alarm set to ring three times a day as a reminder. When the alarm goes off, it continues to ring until Greg turns it off. The first time Greg's alarm went off today, it rang four times. The second time Greg's alarm went off, it rang for three times as long as the first time. The third time Greg's alarm went off, it rang for half as long as the second time. How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?", "solutions": [22]}
{"id_chain": [63], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.": 1596}, "problem": "Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $140 per month. The streaming company charges Alena the initial amount for the first half of the year. For the second half of the year, the streaming company charged Alena 10% less than they did in the first half. Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.", "solutions": [1596]}
{"id_chain": [68], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?": 36}, "problem": "There are twice as many boys as girls at Dr. Wertz's school. There are 60 girls and 5 students to every teacher.  How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?", "solutions": [36]}
{"id_chain": [44], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What is Charlie's net profit?": 20}, "problem": "Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax candles that Charlie buys, he can make 10 tapered candles. One pound of beeswax and the wicks cost $10.00 in supplies. Charlie sells each candle for $2.00. Charlie makes and sells 20 candles. What is Charlie's net profit?", "solutions": [20]}
{"id_chain": [8], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45}, "problem": "John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 60 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home. John tries to get home in 4 hours but spends the first 2 hours in standstill traffic.  John spends the next half-hour driving at a speed of 30mph, before being able to drive the remaining time of the 4 hours going at 80 mph. How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?", "solutions": [45]}
{"id_chain": [28], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?": 25}, "problem": "Henry made two stops during his 60-mile bike trip. Henry first stopped after 20 miles. Henry's second stop was 15 miles before the end of his bike trip. How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?", "solutions": [25]}
{"id_chain": [45], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104}, "problem": "Meredith is a freelance blogger who writes about health topics and submits to clients each day as her permanent job. A blog article takes Meredith an average of 4 hours to research and write about. Last week, Meredith wrote 5 articles on Monday and  2/5 times more articles on Tuesday than on Monday. On Wednesday, Meredith wrote twice the number of articles she wrote on Tuesday. Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.", "solutions": [104]}
{"id_chain": [89], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24}, "problem": "Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 16 friends. Gift bags cost $2 each. How much will Christina spend on gift bags?", "solutions": [24]}
{"id_chain": [34], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23}, "problem": "Siobhan has 2 fewer jewels than Aaron. Aaron has 5 more jewels than half of Raymond's jewels. Raymond has 40 jewels. How many jewels does Siobhan have?", "solutions": [23]}
{"id_chain": [32], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35}, "problem": "Joseph takes care of 10 dogs. Each dog that Joseph takes care of takes .5 hours a day to walk and take care of their business. How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?", "solutions": [35]}
{"id_chain": [38], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How fast does Jack run?": 10}, "problem": "Jack runs 60 miles a week. Jack runs 3 days a week.  Jack runs 3 hours the first day of running and half as much the other two days he runs. How fast does Jack run?", "solutions": [10]}
{"id_chain": [61], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430}, "problem": "Julia buys a brooch for her daughter.  Julia pays $500 for the material to make the brooch for her daughter and then another $800 for the jeweler to construct it. After paying the jeweler, Julia pays another 10% of what she has paid so far in total to get it insured. How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?", "solutions": [1430]}
{"id_chain": [88], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many copies did Harald sell?": 8000}, "problem": "Marilyn's first record sold 10 times as many copies as Harald's. Marilyn and Harald sold 88000 copies combined. How many copies did Harald sell?", "solutions": [8000]}
{"id_chain": [35], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total points did Mike score?": 9}, "problem": "Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 4 points. In the second 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 25% more points than in the first 20 minutes. How many total points did Mike score?", "solutions": [9]}
{"id_chain": [24], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26}, "problem": "Kyle bought last year's best-selling book for $19.50. The price of the book Kyle bought had a 25% discount from the original price. What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?", "solutions": [26]}
{"id_chain": [79], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much does the grooming cost?": 70}, "problem": "Jeremy adopts a dog.  He takes the dog to the groomer, which costs $100. The groomer offers him a 30% discount for being a new customer. How much does the grooming cost?", "solutions": [70]}
{"id_chain": [16], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230}, "problem": "Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 80 miles. On their second day, the two trains travel northwards, covering 150 miles. What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?", "solutions": [230]}
{"id_chain": [90], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "Ted the T-Rex was planning to bring potato salad to the dinosaur picnic.  Ted knows that an adult dinosaur will eat 10 lbs of potato salad, and a child will eat half as much as an adult. There will be 20 adults and 5 children at the dinosaur picnic. How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?", "solutions": [225]}
{"id_chain": [82], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623}, "problem": "Grace weighs 125 pounds. Alex weighs 2 pounds less than 4 times what Grace weighs. What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?", "solutions": [623]}
{"id_chain": [69, 42], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How many pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests?": 26}, "problem": "If it is true that Bailey started with 50 dollars, then the following is true: [Grandma Jones baked 5 apple pies for the fireman's luncheon.  Grandma Jones cut each pie into 6 pieces and set the five pies out on the buffet table for the guests to serve themselves.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Grandma Jones baked 5 apple pies for the fireman's luncheon.  Grandma Jones cut each pie into 8 pieces and set the five pies out on the buffet table for the guests to serve themselves.] At the end of the evening, after the guests had taken and eaten their pieces of pie, there were 14 pieces of pie remaining. Bailey starts with a certain amount of money. Bailey receives a weekly allowance of $5 for 8 weeks. At the end of 8 weeks, Bailey has a total of $100. How many pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests?", "solutions": [26, 60]}
{"id_chain": [89, 35], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24}, "problem": "If it is true that Christina will spend 22 dollars on gift bags, then the following is true: [Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 3 points.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 4 points.] In the second 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 25% more points than in the first 20 minutes. Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 16 friends. Gift bags cost $2 each. How many total points did Mike score?", "solutions": [9, 24]}
{"id_chain": [79, 39], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70}, "problem": "If it is true that The grooming costs 70 dollars, then the following is true: [Dana can run at a rate of speed four times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Dana can run at a rate of speed three times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run.] Dana can skip at 3 miles per hour. Dana spends one-third of the time running and two-thirds of the time walking. Jeremy adopts a dog.  He takes the dog to the groomer, which costs $100. The groomer offers him a 30% discount for being a new customer. How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?", "solutions": [18, 70]}
{"id_chain": [73, 64], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255}, "problem": "If it is true that Shiela will pay 235 dollars per month for the cell phones, then the following is true: [Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 200 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 100 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again.] The owner's manual for Sophia's car says that the car's tank holds 12 gallons of gas. Shiela bought five cell phones for $150 each for a 3-month installment. A 2% interest will be charged for each cell phone Shiela buys. How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?", "solutions": [300, 255]}
{"id_chain": [80, 41], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10, "How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 200}, "problem": "If it is true that There were 10 liters of water left after the two girls and the boy got water, then the following is true: [The great dragon, Perg, sat high atop mount Farbo, breathing fire upon anything within a distance of 1000 feet.] Otherwise, the following is true: [The great dragon, Perg, sat high atop mount Farbo, breathing fire upon anything within a distance of 1150 feet.] Polly could throw the gold javelin, the only known weapon that could sleigh the dragon, for a distance of 400 feet, well within the reach of the dragon's flames.  But when Polly held the sapphire gemstone, she could throw the javelin three times farther than when not holding the gemstone. Polly is holding the gemstone. Two girls each got 1/6 of the 24 liters of water. After the two girls got water, a boy got 6 liters of water. How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?", "solutions": [200, 10]}
{"id_chain": [67, 85], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 44}, "problem": "If it is true that There were 595 gems in the buried treasure chest, then the following is true: [Gene is sewing a quilt out of old souvenir t-shirts. Gene has one shirt from each vacation he has been on.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Gene is sewing a quilt out of old souvenir t-shirts. Gene has two shirts from each vacation he has been on.] Every shirt Gene makes is its own quilt block. Each row of the quilt Gene makes is made of blocks from a different year of vacations. Gene goes on four vacations a year and has been vacationing since he was 23 years old. Gene is now 34. A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 175 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest. How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?", "solutions": [595, 44]}
{"id_chain": [90, 63], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.": 1596, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "If it is true that Ted needs to bring 225 pounds of potato salad, then the following is true: [Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $140 per month.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $130 per month.] The streaming company charges Alena the initial amount for the first half of the year. For the second half of the year, the streaming company charged Alena 10% less than they did in the first half. Ted the T-Rex was planning to bring potato salad to the dinosaur picnic.  Ted knows that an adult dinosaur will eat 10 lbs of potato salad, and a child will eat half as much as an adult. There will be 20 adults and 5 children at the dinosaur picnic. Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.", "solutions": [1596, 225]}
{"id_chain": [43, 18], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 4, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 36}, "problem": "If it is true that You can eat 36 grams of chips without exceeding your calorie limit today, then the following is true: [Claire makes a 2 egg omelet every morning for breakfast.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Claire makes a 3 egg omelet every morning for breakfast.]  According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 250 calories per serving. A 300g bag has 5 servings. Assume your daily calorie target is 2000. Assume you have already eaten 1800 calories today. How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?", "solutions": [7, 48]}
{"id_chain": [76, 71], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 60, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5}, "problem": "If it is true that Cecilia will use 5 bags of dog food in the first year, then the following is true: [Kelian has two recipes for preparing dishes, one having 20 instructions and the second one having twice as many instructions as the first one.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Kelian has two recipes for preparing dishes, one having 18 instructions and the second one having twice as many instructions as the first one.]  Cecilia just bought a new puppy. According to her veterinarian, Cecilia has to feed the puppy 1 cup of dog food every day for the first 180 days. After 180 days, Cecilia has to feed the puppy 2 cups of dog food every day for the rest of its life. One bag of dog food contains 110 cups. How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?", "solutions": [60, 5]}
{"id_chain": [11, 16], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much did Toula have to pay in total?": 694, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230}, "problem": "If it is true that Toula had to pay 696 dollars in total, then the following is true: [Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 90 miles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 80 miles.] On their second day, the two trains travel northwards, covering 150 miles. Toula went to the bakery and bought various types of pastries. Toula bought 3 dozen donuts which cost $68 per dozen, 2 dozen mini cupcakes which cost $80 per dozen, and 6 dozen mini cheesecakes for $55 per dozen. What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?", "solutions": [694, 230]}
{"id_chain": [45, 68], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?": 36}, "problem": "If it is true that Meredith spent 104 hours writing articles in three days, then the following is true: [There are twice as many boys as girls at Dr. Wertz's school. There are 60 girls and 5 students to every teacher.] Otherwise, the following is true: [There are three times as many boys as girls at Dr. Wertz's school. There are 60 girls and 5 students to every teacher.]  Meredith is a freelance blogger who writes about health topics and submits to clients each day as her permanent job. A blog article takes Meredith an average of 4 hours to research and write about. Last week, Meredith wrote 5 articles on Monday and  2/5 times more articles on Tuesday than on Monday. On Wednesday, Meredith wrote twice the number of articles she wrote on Tuesday. How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?", "solutions": [104, 36]}
{"id_chain": [39, 43], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48}, "problem": "If it is true that Dana can travel 18 miles in six hours, then the following is true: [According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 250 calories per serving.] Otherwise, the following is true: [According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 300 calories per serving.] A 300g bag has 5 servings. Assume your daily calorie target is 2000. Assume you have already eaten 1800 calories today. Dana can run at a rate of speed four times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run. Dana can skip at 3 miles per hour. Dana spends one-third of the time running and two-thirds of the time walking. How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?", "solutions": [18, 48]}
{"id_chain": [4, 13], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 18}, "problem": "If it is true that Wendi needs to give her chickens 30 cups of feed in the final meal of the day, then the following is true: [Melanie is a door-to-door saleswoman. Melanie sold a half of her vacuum cleaners at the green house, 2 more to the red house, and half of what was left at the orange house.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Melanie is a door-to-door saleswoman. Melanie sold a third of her vacuum cleaners at the green house, 2 more to the red house, and half of what was left at the orange house.] Melanie has 5 vacuum cleaners left. Every day, Wendi feeds each of her chickens three cups of mixed chicken feed, containing seeds, mealworms and vegetables to help keep them healthy. Wendi gives her chickens their feed in three separate meals. In the morning, Wendi gives her flock of chickens 15 cups of feed.  In the afternoon, Wendi gives her chickens another 25 cups of feed. The size of Wendi's flock is 20 chickens. How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?", "solutions": [20, 18]}
{"id_chain": [43, 63], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 36, "Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.": 1482}, "problem": "If it is true that You can eat 36 grams of chips without exceeding your calorie limit today, then the following is true: [Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $130 per month.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $140 per month.] The streaming company charges Alena the initial amount for the first half of the year. For the second half of the year, the streaming company charged Alena 10% less than they did in the first half. According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 250 calories per serving. A 300g bag has 5 servings. Assume your daily calorie target is 2000. Assume you have already eaten 1800 calories today. Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.", "solutions": [48, 1596]}
{"id_chain": [9, 16], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230}, "problem": "If it is true that Eliza's earnings for this week are 460 dollars, then the following is true: [Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 80 miles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 90 miles.] On their second day, the two trains travel northwards, covering 150 miles. Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $10. Eliza also receives an overtime pay of 1.2 times her regular hourly rate. Eliza worked for 45 hours this week. What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?", "solutions": [460, 230]}
{"id_chain": [73, 60], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17}, "problem": "If it is true that Shiela will pay 235 dollars per month for the cell phones, then the following is true: [A basket contains 20 oranges among which 1 is bad, 20% are unripe, 2 are sour and the rest are good.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A basket contains 25 oranges among which 1 is bad, 20% are unripe, 2 are sour and the rest are good.]  Shiela bought five cell phones for $150 each for a 3-month installment. A 2% interest will be charged for each cell phone Shiela buys. How many oranges in the basket are good?", "solutions": [17, 255]}
{"id_chain": [60, 49], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17}, "problem": "If it is true that 17 oranges in the basket are good, then the following is true: [Richard lives in an apartment building with 15 floors.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Richard lives in an apartment building with 20 floors.] Each floor of Richard's apartment building contains 8 units, and 3/4 of the building is occupied. A basket contains 25 oranges among which 1 is bad, 20% are unripe, 2 are sour and the rest are good. What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?", "solutions": [30, 17]}
{"id_chain": [73, 44], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20}, "problem": "If it is true that Shiela will pay 255 dollars per month for the cell phones, then the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax candles that Charlie buys, he can make 10 tapered candles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax Charlie buys, he can make 20 tapered candles.] One pound of beeswax and the wicks cost $10.00 in supplies. Charlie sells each candle for $2.00. Charlie makes and sells 20 candles. Shiela bought five cell phones for $150 each for a 3-month installment. A 2% interest will be charged for each cell phone Shiela buys. What is Charlie's net profit?", "solutions": [20, 255]}
{"id_chain": [46, 82], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623}, "problem": "If it is true that There were 157 post-it notes in the package Candice purchased, then the following is true: [Grace weighs 100 pounds.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Grace weighs 125 pounds.] Alex weighs 2 pounds less than 4 times what Grace weighs. Candice put 80 post-it notes in her purse before she headed out to her job at the coffee shop. On her way, Candice stopped off at the store and purchased a package of Post-it notes;  At work, she placed a single Post-it note on each of 220 different cups of coffee. Candice had 23 post-it notes remaining overall. What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?", "solutions": [163, 623]}
{"id_chain": [43, 41], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 50, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 36}, "problem": "If it is true that You can eat 36 grams of chips without exceeding your calorie limit today, then the following is true: [The great dragon, Perg, sat high atop mount Farbo, breathing fire upon anything within a distance of 1150 feet.] Otherwise, the following is true: [The great dragon, Perg, sat high atop mount Farbo, breathing fire upon anything within a distance of 1000 feet.] Polly could throw the gold javelin, the only known weapon that could sleigh the dragon, for a distance of 400 feet, well within the reach of the dragon's flames.  But when Polly held the sapphire gemstone, she could throw the javelin three times farther than when not holding the gemstone. Polly is holding the gemstone. According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 250 calories per serving. A 300g bag has 5 servings. Assume your daily calorie target is 2000. Assume you have already eaten 1800 calories today. How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?", "solutions": [200, 48]}
{"id_chain": [6, 83], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260, "How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?": 600}, "problem": "If it is true that Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle together have 280 sheep, then the following is true: [Dan plants 2 rose bushes.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Dan plants 3 rose bushes.] Each rose bush Dan plants has 25 roses. Each rose on Dan's rose bushes has 8 thorns. Toulouse has twice as many sheep as Charleston. Charleston has 4 times as many sheep as Seattle. Seattle has 20 sheep. How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?", "solutions": [260, 600]}
{"id_chain": [47, 1], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How much did Justin spend on ties?": 800}, "problem": "If it is true that Justin spent 1000 dollars on ties, then the following is true: [A robe takes 4 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A robe takes 2 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.]  Justin buys twice as many red ties as blue ties. The red ties that Justing bought cost 50% more than blue ties.  Justin spent $200 on blue ties that cost $40 each. How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?", "solutions": [3, 800]}
{"id_chain": [75, 44], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20}, "problem": "If it is true that The average square footage of a level of Luke's sandcastle is 80 square feet, then the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax Charlie buys, he can make 20 tapered candles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax candles that Charlie buys, he can make 10 tapered candles.] One pound of beeswax and the wicks cost $10.00 in supplies. Charlie sells each candle for $2.00. Charlie makes and sells 20 candles. Luke is spending time at the beach building sandcastles. Luke eventually notices that each level of a sandcastle will have half the square footage as the level below it. Luke makes a 4 leveled sandcastle. The top level of the sandcastle that Luke makes has a square footage of 16. What is Charlie's net profit?", "solutions": [20, 60]}
{"id_chain": [44, 50], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What is Charlie's net profit?": 20, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294}, "problem": "If it is true that Charlie's net profit is 30 dollars, then the following is true: [Lloyd has an egg farm. Lloyd's chickens produce 273 eggs per day and he sells them for $2 per dozen.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Lloyd has an egg farm. Lloyd's chickens produce 252 eggs per day and he sells them for $2 per dozen.]  Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax candles that Charlie buys, he can make 10 tapered candles. One pound of beeswax and the wicks cost $10.00 in supplies. Charlie sells each candle for $2.00. Charlie makes and sells 20 candles. How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?", "solutions": [20, 294]}
{"id_chain": [60, 37], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17}, "problem": "If it is true that 17 oranges in the basket are good, then the following is true: [Joshua plans to sell all his toys and use the money to buy video games. Joshua has 13 lego sets and he sells them for $15 each.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Joshua plans to sell all his toys and use the money to buy video games. Joshua has 13 lego sets and he sells them for $16 each.] Joshua ends up buying 8 video games for $20 each and has $5 left. A basket contains 25 oranges among which 1 is bad, 20% are unripe, 2 are sour and the rest are good. How many lego sets does Joshua still have?", "solutions": [2, 17]}
{"id_chain": [82, 92, 17], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's Jill's annual salary?": 57500, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How old is Jackson?": 4}, "problem": "If it is true that Jackson is 4 years old, then the following is true: [Jill gets paid $20 per hour to teach and $30 to be a cheerleading coach.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Jill gets paid $24 per hour to teach and $30 to be a cheerleading coach.] Jill works 50 weeks per year. Jill works 35 hours per week as a teacher and 15 hours per week as a coach. If it is true that The combined weight of Alex and Grace is 613 pounds, then the following is true: [Emily has 4 kids named Amy, Jackson, Corey, and Jason. Amy is 6 years older than Jackson and 2 years younger than Corey.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Emily has 4 kids named Amy, Jackson, Corey, and Jason. Amy is 5 years older than Jackson and 2 years younger than Corey.] Jason is 10. Jason is 1 year younger than Corey. Grace weighs 125 pounds. Alex weighs 2 pounds less than 4 times what Grace weighs. What's Jill's annual salary?", "solutions": [57500, 623, 4]}
{"id_chain": [45, 52, 67], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595}, "problem": "If it is true that Uriah needs to remove 12 toys, then the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 200 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 175 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.]  If it is true that Meredith spent 104 hours writing articles in three days, then the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 15 pounds from it.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 20 pounds from it.] Uriah's comic books weigh 1/4 pound each and his toys weigh 1/2 pound each. Uriah removes 30 comic books. Meredith is a freelance blogger who writes about health topics and submits to clients each day as her permanent job. A blog article takes Meredith an average of 4 hours to research and write about. Last week, Meredith wrote 5 articles on Monday and  2/5 times more articles on Tuesday than on Monday. On Wednesday, Meredith wrote twice the number of articles she wrote on Tuesday. How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?", "solutions": [104, 15, 595]}
{"id_chain": [16, 26, 3], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total meters does James run per week?": 540, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243}, "problem": "If it is true that Mishka spent 243 dollars total on all of the clothing items combined, then the following is true: [James decides to run 3 sprints 3 times a week.] Otherwise, the following is true: [James decides to run 2 sprints 3 times a week.] James runs 60 meters each sprint. If it is true that The distance covered by each train in the two days is 330 miles, then the following is true: [Mishka bought 2 pairs of shorts, 3 pairs of pants, and 3 pairs of shoes.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Mishka bought 3 pairs of shorts, 3 pairs of pants, and 3 pairs of shoes.] One pair of shorts that Mishka bought costs $16.50. One pair of pants that Mishka bought costs $22.50 and one pair of shoes costs $42. Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 80 miles. On their second day, the two trains travel northwards, covering 150 miles. How many total meters does James run per week?", "solutions": [540, 230, 243]}
{"id_chain": [37, 22, 67], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595}, "problem": "If it is true that Billy sold 7 DVDs on Tuesday, then the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 175 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 200 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.]  If it is true that Joshua still has 2 lego sets, then the following is true: [Billy sells DVDs. Billy has 8 customers on Tuesday. Billy's first 3 customers buy one DVD each.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Billy sells DVDs. He has 8 customers on Tuesday. Billy first 3 customers buy two DVDs each.] Billy's next 2 customers buy 2 DVDs each.  Billy's last 3 customers don't buy any DVDs. Joshua plans to sell all his toys and use the money to buy video games. Joshua has 13 lego sets and he sells them for $15 each. Joshua ends up buying 8 video games for $20 each and has $5 left. How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?", "solutions": [7, 2, 595]}
{"id_chain": [16, 6, 89], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 340, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24}, "problem": "If it is true that Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle together have 280 sheep, then the following is true: [Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 20 friends.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 16 friends.] Gift bags cost $2 each. If it is true that The distance covered by each train in the two days is 230 miles, then the following is true: [Toulouse has twice as many sheep as Charleston.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Toulouse has three times as many sheep as Charleston.] Charleston has 4 times as many sheep as Seattle. Seattle has 20 sheep. Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 80 miles. On their second day, the two trains travel northwards, covering 150 miles. How much will Christina spend on gift bags?", "solutions": [260, 230, 24]}
{"id_chain": [1, 23, 71], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 60}, "problem": "If it is true that A candle will be 8 centimeters shorter after burning from one o'clock PM to five o'clock PM, then the following is true: [Kelian has two recipes for preparing dishes, one having 20 instructions and the second one having twice as many instructions as the first one.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Kelian has two recipes for preparing dishes, one having 18 instructions and the second one having twice as many instructions as the first one.]  If it is true that A robe takes 4 bolts of fiber in total, then the following is true: [A candle melts by 3 centimeters every hour that it burns.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A candle melts by 2 centimeters every hour that it burns.]  A robe takes 2 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber. How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?", "solutions": [3, 8, 60]}
{"id_chain": [8, 54, 52], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How many kittens does the Doubtfire family now have?": 40}, "problem": "If it is true that The Doubtfire family now has 40 kittens, then the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 15 pounds from it.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 20 pounds from it.] Uriah's comic books weigh 1/4 pound each and his toys weigh 1/2 pound each. Uriah removes 30 comic books. If it is true that John is 45 miles from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by, then the following is true: [The Doubtfire sisters are driving home with 7 kittens adopted from the local animal shelter when their mother calls to inform them that their two house cats have just had kittens.] Otherwise, the following is true: [The Doubtfire sisters are driving home with 9 kittens adopted from the local animal shelter when their mother calls to inform them that their two house cats have just had kittens.] The mother of the Doubtfire sisters say that Patchy, the first cat, has had thrice the number of adopted kittens, while Trixie, the other cat, has had 12. John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 60 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home. John tries to get home in 4 hours but spends the first 2 hours in standstill traffic.  John spends the next half-hour driving at a speed of 30mph, before being able to drive the remaining time of the 4 hours going at 80 mph. How many toys does Uriah need to remove?", "solutions": [45, 15, 40]}
{"id_chain": [26, 83, 64], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?": 600}, "problem": "If it is true that There are 650 thorns in total on all of Dan's roses, then the following is true: [Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 200 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 100 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again.] The owner's manual for Sophia's car says that the car's tank holds 12 gallons of gas. If it is true that Mishka spent 247 dollars total on all of the clothing items combined, then the following is true: [Dan plants 2 rose bushes.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Dan plants 3 rose bushes.] Each rose bush Dan plants has 25 roses. Each rose on Dan's rose bushes has 8 thorns. Mishka bought 3 pairs of shorts, 3 pairs of pants, and 3 pairs of shoes. One pair of shorts that Mishka bought costs $16.50. One pair of pants that Mishka bought costs $22.50 and one pair of shoes costs $42. How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?", "solutions": [243, 300, 600]}
{"id_chain": [73, 6, 48], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255}, "problem": "If it is true that Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle together have 260 sheep, then the following is true: [Tracy used a piece of wire 4 feet long to support tomato plants in the garden.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Tracy used a piece of wire 6 feet long to support tomato plants in the garden.] The wire that Tracy used was cut into pieces 6 inches long. If it is true that Shiela will pay 255 dollars per month for the cell phones, then the following is true: [Toulouse has twice as many sheep as Charleston.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Toulouse has three times as many sheep as Charleston.] Charleston has 4 times as many sheep as Seattle. Seattle has 20 sheep. Shiela bought five cell phones for $150 each for a 3-month installment. A 2% interest will be charged for each cell phone Shiela buys. How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?", "solutions": [260, 8, 255]}
{"id_chain": [89, 13, 42], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 18, "How many pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests?": 26, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24}, "problem": "If it is true that Melanie started with 18 vacuum cleaners, then the following is true: [Grandma Jones baked 5 apple pies for the fireman's luncheon.  Grandma Jones cut each pie into 8 pieces and set the five pies out on the buffet table for the guests to serve themselves.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Grandma Jones baked 5 apple pies for the fireman's luncheon.  Grandma Jones cut each pie into 6 pieces and set the five pies out on the buffet table for the guests to serve themselves.] At the end of the evening, after the guests had taken and eaten their pieces of pie, there were 14 pieces of pie remaining. If it is true that Christina will spend 24 dollars on gift bags, then the following is true: [Melanie is a door-to-door saleswoman. Melanie sold a third of her vacuum cleaners at the green house, 2 more to the red house, and half of what was left at the orange house.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Melanie is a door-to-door saleswoman. Melanie sold a half of her vacuum cleaners at the green house, 2 more to the red house, and half of what was left at the orange house.] Melanie has 5 vacuum cleaners left. Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 16 friends. Gift bags cost $2 each. How many pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests?", "solutions": [18, 26, 24]}
{"id_chain": [49, 52, 8], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45, "What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15}, "problem": "If it is true that Uriah needs to remove 15 toys, then the following is true: [John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 60 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home.] Otherwise, the following is true: [John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 80 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home.] John tries to get home in 4 hours but spends the first 2 hours in standstill traffic.  John spends the next half-hour driving at a speed of 30mph, before being able to drive the remaining time of the 4 hours going at 80 mph. If it is true that The total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building is 25, then the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 20 pounds from it.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 15 pounds from it.] Uriah's comic books weigh 1/4 pound each and his toys weigh 1/2 pound each. Uriah removes 30 comic books. Richard lives in an apartment building with 15 floors. Each floor of Richard's apartment building contains 8 units, and 3/4 of the building is occupied. How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?", "solutions": [45, 30, 15]}
{"id_chain": [46, 67, 11], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595, "How much did Toula have to pay in total?": 694}, "problem": "If it is true that There were 615 gems in the buried treasure chest, then the following is true: [Toula went to the bakery and bought various types of pastries. She bought 3 dozen donuts which cost $57 per dozen, 2 dozen mini cupcakes which cost $80 per dozen, and 6 dozen mini cheesecakes for $55 per dozen.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Toula went to the bakery and bought various types of pastries. Toula bought 3 dozen donuts which cost $68 per dozen, 2 dozen mini cupcakes which cost $80 per dozen, and 6 dozen mini cheesecakes for $55 per dozen.]  If it is true that There were 157 post-it notes in the package Candice purchased, then the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 200 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 175 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.]  Candice put 80 post-it notes in her purse before she headed out to her job at the coffee shop. On her way, Candice stopped off at the store and purchased a package of Post-it notes;  At work, she placed a single Post-it note on each of 220 different cups of coffee. Candice had 23 post-it notes remaining overall. How much did Toula have to pay in total?", "solutions": [694, 163, 595]}
{"id_chain": [60, 90, 1], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225, "How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3}, "problem": "If it is true that Ted needs to bring 225 pounds of potato salad, then the following is true: [A robe takes 2 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A robe takes 4 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.]  If it is true that 17 oranges in the basket are good, then the following is true: [Ted the T-Rex was planning to bring potato salad to the dinosaur picnic.  Ted knows that an adult dinosaur will eat 10 lbs of potato salad, and a child will eat half as much as an adult.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Ted the T-Rex was planning to bring potato salad to the dinosaur picnic.  Ted knows that an adult dinosaur will eat 8 lbs of potato salad, and a child will eat half as much as an adult.] There will be 20 adults and 5 children at the dinosaur picnic. A basket contains 25 oranges among which 1 is bad, 20% are unripe, 2 are sour and the rest are good. How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?", "solutions": [3, 17, 225]}
{"id_chain": [80, 4, 33], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How many gold coins does Gretchen have?": 70, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10}, "problem": "If it is true that Wendi needs to give her chickens 20 cups of feed in the final meal of the day, then the following is true: [Gretchen has 110 coins.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Gretchen has 90 coins.] Gretchen has 30 more gold coins than silver coins. If it is true that There were 10 liters of water left after the two girls and the boy got water, then the following is true: [Every day, Wendi feeds each of her chickens three cups of mixed chicken feed, containing seeds, mealworms and vegetables to help keep them healthy.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Every day, Wendi feeds each of her chickens four cups of mixed chicken feed, containing seeds, mealworms and vegetables to help keep them healthy.] Wendi gives her chickens their feed in three separate meals. In the morning, Wendi gives her flock of chickens 15 cups of feed.  In the afternoon, Wendi gives her chickens another 25 cups of feed. The size of Wendi's flock is 20 chickens. Two girls each got 1/6 of the 24 liters of water. After the two girls got water, a boy got 6 liters of water. How many gold coins does Gretchen have?", "solutions": [20, 70, 10]}
{"id_chain": [52, 43, 46], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 36, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 173, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15}, "problem": "If it is true that You can eat 36 grams of chips without exceeding your calorie limit today, then the following is true: [Candice put 70 post-it notes in her purse before she headed out to her job at the coffee shop.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Candice put 80 post-it notes in her purse before she headed out to her job at the coffee shop.] On her way, Candice stopped off at the store and purchased a package of Post-it notes;  At work, she placed a single Post-it note on each of 220 different cups of coffee. Candice had 23 post-it notes remaining overall. If it is true that Uriah needs to remove 12 toys, then the following is true: [According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 300 calories per serving.] Otherwise, the following is true: [According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 250 calories per serving.] A 300g bag has 5 servings. Assume your daily calorie target is 2000. Assume you have already eaten 1800 calories today. Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 15 pounds from it. Uriah's comic books weigh 1/4 pound each and his toys weigh 1/2 pound each. Uriah removes 30 comic books. How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?", "solutions": [48, 163, 15]}
{"id_chain": [23, 89, 92], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24, "How old is Jackson?": 4}, "problem": "If it is true that Christina will spend 22 dollars on gift bags, then the following is true: [Emily has 4 kids named Amy, Jackson, Corey, and Jason. Amy is 6 years older than Jackson and 2 years younger than Corey.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Emily has 4 kids named Amy, Jackson, Corey, and Jason. Amy is 5 years older than Jackson and 2 years younger than Corey.] Jason is 10. Jason is 1 year younger than Corey. If it is true that A candle will be 8 centimeters shorter after burning from one o'clock PM to five o'clock PM, then the following is true: [Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 16 friends.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 20 friends.] Gift bags cost $2 each. A candle melts by 2 centimeters every hour that it burns. How old is Jackson?", "solutions": [8, 24, 4]}
{"id_chain": [58, 8, 65], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 57, "How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45, "How many hours does Jim spend on TV and reading in four weeks?": 36}, "problem": "If it is true that John is 45 miles from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by, then the following is true: [Jim spends 2 hours watching TV and then decides to go to bed and reads for half as long.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Jim spends 4 hours watching TV and then decides to go to bed and reads for half as long.] Jim watches TV and read 3 times a week. If it is true that The final price of Stephen's groceries after the extra fees was 57 dollars, then the following is true: [John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 60 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home.] Otherwise, the following is true: [John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 80 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home.] John tries to get home in 4 hours but spends the first 2 hours in standstill traffic.  John spends the next half-hour driving at a speed of 30mph, before being able to drive the remaining time of the 4 hours going at 80 mph. Stephen placed an online order for groceries.  Stephen's final grocery bill came to $40.00. Because this was through a delivery vendor, they tacked on a 25% fee to Stephen's final total for groceries and charged him $3.00 in delivery fees.  Stephen also added a $4.00 tip for his groceries. How many hours does Jim spend on TV and reading in four weeks?", "solutions": [45, 57, 36]}
{"id_chain": [25, 26, 82], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623}, "problem": "If it is true that Mishka spent 247 dollars total on all of the clothing items combined, then the following is true: [Grace weighs 100 pounds.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Grace weighs 125 pounds.] Alex weighs 2 pounds less than 4 times what Grace weighs. If it is true that Marie ordered 3 boxes of pizza, then the following is true: [Mishka bought 2 pairs of shorts, 3 pairs of pants, and 3 pairs of shoes.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Mishka bought 3 pairs of shorts, 3 pairs of pants, and 3 pairs of shoes.] One pair of shorts that Mishka bought costs $16.50. One pair of pants that Mishka bought costs $22.50 and one pair of shoes costs $42. Marie ordered one chicken meal that costs $12, 5 packs of milk that costs $3 each, 4 apples that cost $1.50 each, and some boxes of pizza. Marie paid a total of $50. Each box of pizza that Marie bought costs $8.50. What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?", "solutions": [2, 243, 623]}
{"id_chain": [49, 45, 59], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": 187}, "problem": "If it is true that Meredith spent 104 hours writing articles in three days, then the following is true: [A raspberry bush has 6 clusters of 20 fruit each and 67 individual fruit scattered across the bush.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A raspberry bush has 5 clusters of 20 fruit each and 67 individual fruit scattered across the bush.]  If it is true that The total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building is 25, then the following is true: [Meredith is a freelance blogger who writes about health topics and submits to clients each day as her permanent job. A blog article takes Meredith an average of 5 hours to research and write about.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Meredith is a freelance blogger who writes about health topics and submits to clients each day as her permanent job. A blog article takes Meredith an average of 4 hours to research and write about.] Last week, Meredith wrote 5 articles on Monday and  2/5 times more articles on Tuesday than on Monday. On Wednesday, Meredith wrote twice the number of articles she wrote on Tuesday. Richard lives in an apartment building with 15 floors. Each floor of Richard's apartment building contains 8 units, and 3/4 of the building is occupied. How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?", "solutions": [104, 30, 187]}
{"id_chain": [35, 28, 81], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?": 25, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17}, "problem": "If it is true that Henry traveled 27 miles between his first and second stops, then the following is true: [Christopher had 12 stickers.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Christopher had 10 stickers.] Christopher bought 21 stickers from a store in the mall and got 23 stickers for his birthday. Then Christopher gave 9 of the stickers to his sister and used 28 to decorate a greeting card. If it is true that Mike scored 9 total points, then the following is true: [Henry made two stops during his 60-mile bike trip.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Henry made two stops during his 75-mile bike trip.] Henry first stopped after 20 miles. Henry's second stop was 15 miles before the end of his bike trip. Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 4 points. In the second 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 25% more points than in the first 20 minutes. How many stickers does Christopher have left?", "solutions": [25, 9, 17]}
{"id_chain": [64, 39, 90], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 20, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "If it is true that Dana can travel 18 miles in six hours, then the following is true: [Ted the T-Rex was planning to bring potato salad to the dinosaur picnic.  Ted knows that an adult dinosaur will eat 10 lbs of potato salad, and a child will eat half as much as an adult.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Ted the T-Rex was planning to bring potato salad to the dinosaur picnic.  Ted knows that an adult dinosaur will eat 8 lbs of potato salad, and a child will eat half as much as an adult.] There will be 20 adults and 5 children at the dinosaur picnic. If it is true that Sophia can drive 250 miles on a single tank of gas, then the following is true: [Dana can run at a rate of speed three times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Dana can run at a rate of speed four times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run.] Dana can skip at 3 miles per hour. Dana spends one-third of the time running and two-thirds of the time walking. Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 100 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again. The owner's manual for Sophia's car says that the car's tank holds 12 gallons of gas. How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?", "solutions": [18, 300, 225]}
{"id_chain": [16, 61, 91], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "If it is true that Julia paid 1570 dollars in total for the brooch, then the following is true: [Jan has four times the number of pets as Marcia.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Jan has three times the number of pets as Marcia.] Marcia has two more pets than Cindy. Cindy has four pets. If it is true that The distance covered by each train in the two days is 230 miles, then the following is true: [Julia buys a brooch for her daughter.  Julia pays $500 for the material to make the brooch for her daughter and then another $800 for the jeweler to construct it.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Julia buys a brooch for her daughter.  Julia pays $700 for the material to make the brooch for her daughter and then another $800 for the jeweler to construct it.] After paying the jeweler, Julia pays another 10% of what she has paid so far in total to get it insured. Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 80 miles. On their second day, the two trains travel northwards, covering 150 miles. How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?", "solutions": [230, 1430, 28]}
{"id_chain": [80, 46, 33], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many gold coins does Gretchen have?": 70, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10}, "problem": "If it is true that There were 163 post-it notes in the package Candice purchased, then the following is true: [Gretchen has 110 coins.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Gretchen has 90 coins.] Gretchen has 30 more gold coins than silver coins. If it is true that There were 7 liters of water left after the two girls and the boy got water, then the following is true: [Candice put 70 post-it notes in her purse before she headed out to her job at the coffee shop.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Candice put 80 post-it notes in her purse before she headed out to her job at the coffee shop.] On her way, Candice stopped off at the store and purchased a package of Post-it notes;  At work, she placed a single Post-it note on each of 220 different cups of coffee. Candice had 23 post-it notes remaining overall. Two girls each got 1/6 of the 24 liters of water. After the two girls got water, a boy got 6 liters of water. How many gold coins does Gretchen have?", "solutions": [70, 163, 10]}
{"id_chain": [37, 60, 67], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595}, "problem": "If it is true that 17 oranges in the basket are good, then the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 175 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 200 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.]  If it is true that Joshua still has 2 lego sets, then the following is true: [A basket contains 25 oranges among which 1 is bad, 20% are unripe, 2 are sour and the rest are good.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A basket contains 20 oranges among which 1 is bad, 20% are unripe, 2 are sour and the rest are good.]  Joshua plans to sell all his toys and use the money to buy video games. Joshua has 13 lego sets and he sells them for $15 each. Joshua ends up buying 8 video games for $20 each and has $5 left. How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?", "solutions": [2, 17, 595]}
{"id_chain": [64, 0, 63], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?": 26, "Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.": 1596, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300}, "problem": "If it is true that Janet makes 16 dollars every day at the farmers' market, then the following is true: [Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $130 per month.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $140 per month.] The streaming company charges Alena the initial amount for the first half of the year. For the second half of the year, the streaming company charged Alena 10% less than they did in the first half. If it is true that Sophia can drive 250 miles on a single tank of gas, then the following is true: [Janet\u2019s ducks lay 20 eggs per day.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Janet\u2019s ducks lay 16 eggs per day.] Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 100 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again. The owner's manual for Sophia's car says that the car's tank holds 12 gallons of gas. Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.", "solutions": [18, 1596, 300]}
{"id_chain": [58, 86, 80, 10], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 57, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10, "How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?": 366}, "problem": "If it is true that There were 7 liters of water left after the two girls and the boy got water, then the following is true: [A new program had 70 downloads in the first month.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A new program had 60 downloads in the first month.] The number of the new program's downloads in the second month was three times as many as the downloads in the first month, but then reduced by 30% in the third month. If it is true that Greg's alarm rang 22 times in all, then the following is true: [Two girls each got 1/6 of the 24 liters of water.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Two girls each got 1/6 of the 18 liters of water.] After the two girls got water, a boy got 6 liters of water. If it is true that The final price of Stephen's groceries after the extra fees was 53 dollars, then the following is true: [Greg has an alarm set to ring three times a day as a reminder. When Greg's alarm goes off, it continues to ring until Greg turns it off. The first time Greg's alarm went off today, it rang two times.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Greg has an alarm set to ring three times a day as a reminder. When the alarm goes off, it continues to ring until Greg turns it off. The first time Greg's alarm went off today, it rang four times.] The second time Greg's alarm went off, it rang for three times as long as the first time. The third time Greg's alarm went off, it rang for half as long as the second time. Stephen placed an online order for groceries.  Stephen's final grocery bill came to $40.00. Because this was through a delivery vendor, they tacked on a 25% fee to Stephen's final total for groceries and charged him $3.00 in delivery fees.  Stephen also added a $4.00 tip for his groceries. How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?", "solutions": [366, 57, 10, 22]}
{"id_chain": [22, 23, 41, 43], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 200, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48}, "problem": "If it is true that Polly could stand 200 feet outside the reach of the dragon's flames and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin, then the following is true: [According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 250 calories per serving.] Otherwise, the following is true: [According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 300 calories per serving.] A 300g bag has 5 servings. Assume your daily calorie target is 2000. Assume you have already eaten 1800 calories today. If it is true that A candle will be 8 centimeters shorter after burning from one o'clock PM to five o'clock PM, then the following is true: [The great dragon, Perg, sat high atop mount Farbo, breathing fire upon anything within a distance of 1000 feet.] Otherwise, the following is true: [The great dragon, Perg, sat high atop mount Farbo, breathing fire upon anything within a distance of 1150 feet.] Polly could throw the gold javelin, the only known weapon that could sleigh the dragon, for a distance of 400 feet, well within the reach of the dragon's flames.  But when Polly held the sapphire gemstone, she could throw the javelin three times farther than when not holding the gemstone. Polly is holding the gemstone. If it is true that Billy sold 9 DVDs on Tuesday, then the following is true: [A candle melts by 3 centimeters every hour that it burns.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A candle melts by 2 centimeters every hour that it burns.]  Billy sells DVDs. Billy has 8 customers on Tuesday. Billy's first 3 customers buy one DVD each. Billy's next 2 customers buy 2 DVDs each.  Billy's last 3 customers don't buy any DVDs. How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?", "solutions": [7, 8, 200, 48]}
{"id_chain": [0, 41, 3, 44], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?": 18, "How many total meters does James run per week?": 540, "How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 200, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20}, "problem": "If it is true that James runs 490 total meters per week, then the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax Charlie buys, he can make 20 tapered candles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax candles that Charlie buys, he can make 10 tapered candles.] One pound of beeswax and the wicks cost $10.00 in supplies. Charlie sells each candle for $2.00. Charlie makes and sells 20 candles. If it is true that Polly could stand 200 feet outside the reach of the dragon's flames and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin, then the following is true: [James decides to run 3 sprints 3 times a week.] Otherwise, the following is true: [James decides to run 2 sprints 3 times a week.] James runs 60 meters each sprint. If it is true that Janet makes 16 dollars every day at the farmers' market, then the following is true: [The great dragon, Perg, sat high atop mount Farbo, breathing fire upon anything within a distance of 1150 feet.] Otherwise, the following is true: [The great dragon, Perg, sat high atop mount Farbo, breathing fire upon anything within a distance of 1000 feet.] Polly could throw the gold javelin, the only known weapon that could sleigh the dragon, for a distance of 400 feet, well within the reach of the dragon's flames.  But when Polly held the sapphire gemstone, she could throw the javelin three times farther than when not holding the gemstone. Polly is holding the gemstone. Janet\u2019s ducks lay 16 eggs per day. Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. What is Charlie's net profit?", "solutions": [18, 540, 200, 20]}
{"id_chain": [72, 33, 43, 64], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many gold coins does Gretchen have?": 70, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 221}, "problem": "If it is true that You can eat 48 grams of chips without exceeding your calorie limit today, then the following is true: [Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 100 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 200 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again.] The owner's manual for Sophia's car says that the car's tank holds 12 gallons of gas. If it is true that Gretchen has 70 gold coins, then the following is true: [According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 250 calories per serving.] Otherwise, the following is true: [According to its nutritional info, a bag of chips has 300 calories per serving.] A 300g bag has 5 servings. Assume your daily calorie target is 2000. Assume you have already eaten 1800 calories today. If it is true that Tommy raises 221 dollars, then the following is true: [Gretchen has 110 coins.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Gretchen has 90 coins.] Gretchen has 30 more gold coins than silver coins. Tommy is fundraising for his charity by selling brownies for $3 a slice and cheesecakes for $4 a slice. Tommy sells 43 brownies. Tommy sells 23 slices of cheesecake. How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?", "solutions": [70, 48, 300, 221]}
{"id_chain": [35, 37, 16, 22], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7}, "problem": "If it is true that The distance covered by each train in the two days is 230 miles, then the following is true: [Billy sells DVDs. Billy has 8 customers on Tuesday. Billy's first 3 customers buy one DVD each.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Billy sells DVDs. He has 8 customers on Tuesday. Billy first 3 customers buy two DVDs each.] Billy's next 2 customers buy 2 DVDs each.  Billy's last 3 customers don't buy any DVDs. If it is true that Joshua still has 2 lego sets, then the following is true: [Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 80 miles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 90 miles.] On their second day, the two trains travel northwards, covering 150 miles. If it is true that Mike scored 8 total points, then the following is true: [Joshua plans to sell all his toys and use the money to buy video games. Joshua has 13 lego sets and he sells them for $16 each.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Joshua plans to sell all his toys and use the money to buy video games. Joshua has 13 lego sets and he sells them for $15 each.] Joshua ends up buying 8 video games for $20 each and has $5 left. Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 4 points. In the second 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 25% more points than in the first 20 minutes. How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?", "solutions": [230, 7, 9, 2]}
{"id_chain": [42, 85, 54, 73], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests?": 26, "How many kittens does the Doubtfire family now have?": 40, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 44}, "problem": "If it is true that The Doubtfire family now has 45 kittens, then the following is true: [Shiela bought five cell phones for $180 each for a 3-month installment.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Shiela bought five cell phones for $150 each for a 3-month installment.] A 2% interest will be charged for each cell phone Shiela buys. If it is true that Gene has 42 quilt blocks in total, then the following is true: [The Doubtfire sisters are driving home with 9 kittens adopted from the local animal shelter when their mother calls to inform them that their two house cats have just had kittens.] Otherwise, the following is true: [The Doubtfire sisters are driving home with 7 kittens adopted from the local animal shelter when their mother calls to inform them that their two house cats have just had kittens.] The mother of the Doubtfire sisters say that Patchy, the first cat, has had thrice the number of adopted kittens, while Trixie, the other cat, has had 12. If it is true that 26 pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests, then the following is true: [Gene is sewing a quilt out of old souvenir t-shirts. Gene has one shirt from each vacation he has been on.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Gene is sewing a quilt out of old souvenir t-shirts. Gene has two shirts from each vacation he has been on.] Every shirt Gene makes is its own quilt block. Each row of the quilt Gene makes is made of blocks from a different year of vacations. Gene goes on four vacations a year and has been vacationing since he was 23 years old. Gene is now 34. Grandma Jones baked 5 apple pies for the fireman's luncheon.  Grandma Jones cut each pie into 8 pieces and set the five pies out on the buffet table for the guests to serve themselves. At the end of the evening, after the guests had taken and eaten their pieces of pie, there were 14 pieces of pie remaining. How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?", "solutions": [26, 40, 255, 44]}
{"id_chain": [67, 9, 45, 69], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60}, "problem": "If it is true that Meredith spent 106 hours writing articles in three days, then the following is true: [Bailey starts with a certain amount of money. Bailey receives a weekly allowance of $8 for 8 weeks.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Bailey starts with a certain amount of money. Bailey receives a weekly allowance of $5 for 8 weeks.] At the end of 8 weeks, Bailey has a total of $100. If it is true that Eliza's earnings for this week are 420 dollars, then the following is true: [Meredith is a freelance blogger who writes about health topics and submits to clients each day as her permanent job. A blog article takes Meredith an average of 5 hours to research and write about.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Meredith is a freelance blogger who writes about health topics and submits to clients each day as her permanent job. A blog article takes Meredith an average of 4 hours to research and write about.] Last week, Meredith wrote 5 articles on Monday and  2/5 times more articles on Tuesday than on Monday. On Wednesday, Meredith wrote twice the number of articles she wrote on Tuesday. If it is true that There were 595 gems in the buried treasure chest, then the following is true: [Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $10.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $11.] Eliza also receives an overtime pay of 1.2 times her regular hourly rate. Eliza worked for 45 hours this week. A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 175 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest. How much money did Bailey start with?", "solutions": [460, 104, 595, 60]}
{"id_chain": [69, 39, 63, 58], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 57, "Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.": 1596, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60}, "problem": "If it is true that Aleena paid 1564 dollars total for the streaming service by the end of the year, then the following is true: [Stephen placed an online order for groceries.  Stephen's final grocery bill came to $37.00.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Stephen placed an online order for groceries.  Stephen's final grocery bill came to $40.00.] Because this was through a delivery vendor, they tacked on a 25% fee to Stephen's final total for groceries and charged him $3.00 in delivery fees.  Stephen also added a $4.00 tip for his groceries. If it is true that Dana can travel 18 miles in six hours, then the following is true: [Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $140 per month.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Aleena subscribed to a streaming service that charges her $130 per month.] The streaming company charges Alena the initial amount for the first half of the year. For the second half of the year, the streaming company charged Alena 10% less than they did in the first half. If it is true that Bailey started with 50 dollars, then the following is true: [Dana can run at a rate of speed three times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Dana can run at a rate of speed four times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run.] Dana can skip at 3 miles per hour. Dana spends one-third of the time running and two-thirds of the time walking. Bailey starts with a certain amount of money. Bailey receives a weekly allowance of $5 for 8 weeks. At the end of 8 weeks, Bailey has a total of $100. After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?", "solutions": [18, 57, 1596, 60]}
{"id_chain": [81, 23, 89, 39], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18}, "problem": "If it is true that Christina will spend 24 dollars on gift bags, then the following is true: [Dana can run at a rate of speed four times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Dana can run at a rate of speed three times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run.] Dana can skip at 3 miles per hour. Dana spends one-third of the time running and two-thirds of the time walking. If it is true that A candle will be 8 centimeters shorter after burning from one o'clock PM to five o'clock PM, then the following is true: [Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 16 friends.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Christina is planning a birthday party and needs .75 gift bags per invited guest, because 1/4 of attendees don't show up. Christina invited 20 friends.] Gift bags cost $2 each. If it is true that Christopher has 17 stickers left, then the following is true: [A candle melts by 2 centimeters every hour that it burns.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A candle melts by 3 centimeters every hour that it burns.]  Christopher had 10 stickers. Christopher bought 21 stickers from a store in the mall and got 23 stickers for his birthday. Then Christopher gave 9 of the stickers to his sister and used 28 to decorate a greeting card. How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?", "solutions": [8, 18, 17, 24]}
{"id_chain": [58, 9, 75, 64], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 53, "How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 506, "What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300}, "problem": "If it is true that The average square footage of a level of Luke's sandcastle is 60 square feet, then the following is true: [Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 100 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Sophia is thinking of taking a road trip in her car, and would like to know how far she can drive on a single tank of gas. Sophia has traveled 200 miles since last filling her tank, and she needed to put in 4 gallons of gas to fill it up again.] The owner's manual for Sophia's car says that the car's tank holds 12 gallons of gas. If it is true that Eliza's earnings for this week are 460 dollars, then the following is true: [Luke is spending time at the beach building sandcastles. Luke eventually notices that each level of a sandcastle will have half the square footage as the level below it.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Luke is spending time at the beach building sandcastles. Luke eventually notices that each level of a sandcastle will have double the square footage as the level below it.] Luke makes a 4 leveled sandcastle. The top level of the sandcastle that Luke makes has a square footage of 16. If it is true that The final price of Stephen's groceries after the extra fees was 53 dollars, then the following is true: [Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $11.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $10.] Eliza also receives an overtime pay of 1.2 times her regular hourly rate. Eliza worked for 45 hours this week. Stephen placed an online order for groceries.  Stephen's final grocery bill came to $40.00. Because this was through a delivery vendor, they tacked on a 25% fee to Stephen's final total for groceries and charged him $3.00 in delivery fees.  Stephen also added a $4.00 tip for his groceries. How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?", "solutions": [460, 57, 300, 60]}
{"id_chain": [6, 86, 44, 24], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260, "What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22}, "problem": "If it is true that Charlie's net profit is 20 dollars, then the following is true: [Kyle bought last year's best-selling book for $19.50.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Kyle bought last year's best-selling book for $21.00.] The price of the book Kyle bought had a 25% discount from the original price. If it is true that Greg's alarm rang 24 times in all, then the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax Charlie buys, he can make 20 tapered candles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax candles that Charlie buys, he can make 10 tapered candles.] One pound of beeswax and the wicks cost $10.00 in supplies. Charlie sells each candle for $2.00. Charlie makes and sells 20 candles. If it is true that Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle together have 260 sheep, then the following is true: [Greg has an alarm set to ring three times a day as a reminder. When the alarm goes off, it continues to ring until Greg turns it off. The first time Greg's alarm went off today, it rang four times.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Greg has an alarm set to ring three times a day as a reminder. When Greg's alarm goes off, it continues to ring until Greg turns it off. The first time Greg's alarm went off today, it rang two times.] The second time Greg's alarm went off, it rang for three times as long as the first time. The third time Greg's alarm went off, it rang for half as long as the second time. Toulouse has twice as many sheep as Charleston. Charleston has 4 times as many sheep as Seattle. Seattle has 20 sheep. What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?", "solutions": [260, 26, 20, 22]}
{"id_chain": [10, 81, 29, 47], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?": 366, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How much did Justin spend on ties?": 800, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17}, "problem": "If it is true that The boots that Gloria came across are 104 dollars, then the following is true: [Justin buys twice as many red ties as blue ties.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Justin buys three times as many red ties as blue ties.] The red ties that Justing bought cost 50% more than blue ties.  Justin spent $200 on blue ties that cost $40 each. If it is true that Christopher has 17 stickers left, then the following is true: [Gloria is shoe shopping when she comes across a pair of boots that fit her shoe budget. Gloria has to choose between the boots she came across and two pairs of high heels that together cost five dollars less than the boots.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Gloria is shoe shopping when she comes across a pair of boots that fit her shoe budget. Gloria has to choose between the boots she came across and two pairs of high heels that together cost seven dollars less than the boots.] One pair of heels Gloria is looking at costs $33. The other pair of heels that Gloria is looking at costs twice as much as the $33 pair. If it is true that The new program had 366 downloads total over the three months, then the following is true: [Christopher had 10 stickers.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Christopher had 12 stickers.] Christopher bought 21 stickers from a store in the mall and got 23 stickers for his birthday. Then Christopher gave 9 of the stickers to his sister and used 28 to decorate a greeting card. A new program had 60 downloads in the first month. The number of the new program's downloads in the second month was three times as many as the downloads in the first month, but then reduced by 30% in the third month. How much did Justin spend on ties?", "solutions": [366, 104, 800, 17]}
{"id_chain": [90, 1, 35, 52], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "If it is true that Mike scored 8 total points, then the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 20 pounds from it.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 15 pounds from it.] Uriah's comic books weigh 1/4 pound each and his toys weigh 1/2 pound each. Uriah removes 30 comic books. If it is true that A robe takes 3 bolts of fiber in total, then the following is true: [Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 4 points.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 3 points.] In the second 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 25% more points than in the first 20 minutes. If it is true that Ted needs to bring 175 pounds of potato salad, then the following is true: [A robe takes 4 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A robe takes 2 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.]  Ted the T-Rex was planning to bring potato salad to the dinosaur picnic.  Ted knows that an adult dinosaur will eat 10 lbs of potato salad, and a child will eat half as much as an adult. There will be 20 adults and 5 children at the dinosaur picnic. How many toys does Uriah need to remove?", "solutions": [3, 9, 15, 225]}
{"id_chain": [23, 35, 1, 6], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260}, "problem": "If it is true that A robe takes 4 bolts of fiber in total, then the following is true: [Toulouse has three times as many sheep as Charleston.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Toulouse has twice as many sheep as Charleston.] Charleston has 4 times as many sheep as Seattle. Seattle has 20 sheep. If it is true that Mike scored 8 total points, then the following is true: [A robe takes 4 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A robe takes 2 bolts of blue fiber and half that much white fiber.]  If it is true that A candle will be 8 centimeters shorter after burning from one o'clock PM to five o'clock PM, then the following is true: [Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 4 points.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Mike plays ping pong for 40 minutes.  In the first 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 3 points.] In the second 20 minutes of playing ping pong, Mike scores 25% more points than in the first 20 minutes. A candle melts by 2 centimeters every hour that it burns. How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?", "solutions": [3, 260, 8, 9]}
{"id_chain": [58, 55, 10, 9], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 506, "How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?": 427, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 16, "After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 53}, "problem": "If it is true that The new program had 366 downloads total over the three months, then the following is true: [Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $10.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $11.] Eliza also receives an overtime pay of 1.2 times her regular hourly rate. Eliza worked for 45 hours this week. If it is true that Jean can fill 12 bags of lollipops, then the following is true: [A new program had 70 downloads in the first month.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A new program had 60 downloads in the first month.] The number of the new program's downloads in the second month was three times as many as the downloads in the first month, but then reduced by 30% in the third month. If it is true that The final price of Stephen's groceries after the extra fees was 53 dollars, then the following is true: [Jean has 35 lollipops.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Jean has 30 lollipops.] Jean eats 2 of the lollipops. With the remaining lollipops, Jean wants to package 2 lollipops in one bag. Stephen placed an online order for groceries.  Stephen's final grocery bill came to $40.00. Because this was through a delivery vendor, they tacked on a 25% fee to Stephen's final total for groceries and charged him $3.00 in delivery fees.  Stephen also added a $4.00 tip for his groceries. How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?", "solutions": [460, 366, 14, 57]}
{"id_chain": [39, 38, 29, 8], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How fast does Jack run?": 10, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18}, "problem": "If it is true that The boots that Gloria came across are 104 dollars, then the following is true: [John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 60 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home.] Otherwise, the following is true: [John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 80 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home.] John tries to get home in 4 hours but spends the first 2 hours in standstill traffic.  John spends the next half-hour driving at a speed of 30mph, before being able to drive the remaining time of the 4 hours going at 80 mph. If it is true that Jack runs 9 miles per hour, then the following is true: [Gloria is shoe shopping when she comes across a pair of boots that fit her shoe budget. Gloria has to choose between the boots she came across and two pairs of high heels that together cost seven dollars less than the boots.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Gloria is shoe shopping when she comes across a pair of boots that fit her shoe budget. Gloria has to choose between the boots she came across and two pairs of high heels that together cost five dollars less than the boots.] One pair of heels Gloria is looking at costs $33. The other pair of heels that Gloria is looking at costs twice as much as the $33 pair. If it is true that Dana can travel 18 miles in six hours, then the following is true: [Jack runs 60 miles a week.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Jack runs 70 miles a week.] Jack runs 3 days a week.  Jack runs 3 hours the first day of running and half as much the other two days he runs. Dana can run at a rate of speed four times faster than she can walk, but she can skip at a rate of speed that is half as fast as she can run. Dana can skip at 3 miles per hour. Dana spends one-third of the time running and two-thirds of the time walking. How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?", "solutions": [45, 104, 10, 18]}
{"id_chain": [3, 52, 65, 85], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total meters does James run per week?": 540, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 25, "How many hours does Jim spend on TV and reading in four weeks?": 36, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 88}, "problem": "If it is true that Jim spends 28 hours on TV and reading in four weeks, then the following is true: [Gene is sewing a quilt out of old souvenir t-shirts. Gene has two shirts from each vacation he has been on.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Gene is sewing a quilt out of old souvenir t-shirts. Gene has one shirt from each vacation he has been on.] Every shirt Gene makes is its own quilt block. Each row of the quilt Gene makes is made of blocks from a different year of vacations. Gene goes on four vacations a year and has been vacationing since he was 23 years old. Gene is now 34. If it is true that Uriah needs to remove 12 toys, then the following is true: [Jim spends 4 hours watching TV and then decides to go to bed and reads for half as long.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Jim spends 2 hours watching TV and then decides to go to bed and reads for half as long.] Jim watches TV and read 3 times a week. If it is true that James runs 490 total meters per week, then the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 20 pounds from it.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Uriah's book bag is getting too heavy for him. Uriah needs to remove 15 pounds from it.] Uriah's comic books weigh 1/4 pound each and his toys weigh 1/2 pound each. Uriah removes 30 comic books. James decides to run 3 sprints 3 times a week. James runs 60 meters each sprint. How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?", "solutions": [540, 15, 36, 44]}
{"id_chain": [50, 68, 37, 86], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 0, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?": 48, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22}, "problem": "If it is true that Joshua still has 3 lego sets, then the following is true: [Greg has an alarm set to ring three times a day as a reminder. When Greg's alarm goes off, it continues to ring until Greg turns it off. The first time Greg's alarm went off today, it rang two times.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Greg has an alarm set to ring three times a day as a reminder. When the alarm goes off, it continues to ring until Greg turns it off. The first time Greg's alarm went off today, it rang four times.] The second time Greg's alarm went off, it rang for three times as long as the first time. The third time Greg's alarm went off, it rang for half as long as the second time. If it is true that There are 36 teachers in Dr Wertz's school, then the following is true: [Joshua plans to sell all his toys and use the money to buy video games. Joshua has 13 lego sets and he sells them for $15 each.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Joshua plans to sell all his toys and use the money to buy video games. Joshua has 13 lego sets and he sells them for $16 each.] Joshua ends up buying 8 video games for $20 each and has $5 left. If it is true that Lloyd makes 294 dollars on eggs per week, then the following is true: [There are twice as many boys as girls at Dr. Wertz's school. There are 60 girls and 5 students to every teacher.] Otherwise, the following is true: [There are three times as many boys as girls at Dr. Wertz's school. There are 60 girls and 5 students to every teacher.]  Lloyd has an egg farm. Lloyd's chickens produce 252 eggs per day and he sells them for $2 per dozen. How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?", "solutions": [2, 294, 36, 22]}
{"id_chain": [45, 16, 44, 48], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8}, "problem": "If it is true that Charlie's net profit is 30 dollars, then the following is true: [Tracy used a piece of wire 6 feet long to support tomato plants in the garden.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Tracy used a piece of wire 4 feet long to support tomato plants in the garden.] The wire that Tracy used was cut into pieces 6 inches long. If it is true that The distance covered by each train in the two days is 230 miles, then the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax candles that Charlie buys, he can make 10 tapered candles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Charlie wants to sell beeswax candles.  For every pound of beeswax Charlie buys, he can make 20 tapered candles.] One pound of beeswax and the wicks cost $10.00 in supplies. Charlie sells each candle for $2.00. Charlie makes and sells 20 candles. If it is true that Meredith spent 104 hours writing articles in three days, then the following is true: [Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 80 miles.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Two trains leave San Rafael at the same time. The two trains begin traveling westward, both traveling for 90 miles.] On their second day, the two trains travel northwards, covering 150 miles. Meredith is a freelance blogger who writes about health topics and submits to clients each day as her permanent job. A blog article takes Meredith an average of 4 hours to research and write about. Last week, Meredith wrote 5 articles on Monday and  2/5 times more articles on Tuesday than on Monday. On Wednesday, Meredith wrote twice the number of articles she wrote on Tuesday. How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?", "solutions": [230, 20, 104, 8]}
{"id_chain": [8, 9, 69, 67], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45, "How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595}, "problem": "If it is true that Bailey started with 50 dollars, then the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 200 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.] Otherwise, the following is true: [A treasure hunter found a buried treasure chest filled with gems. There were 175 diamonds, 35 fewer rubies than diamonds, and twice the number of emeralds than the rubies in the buried treasure chest.]  If it is true that Eliza's earnings for this week are 420 dollars, then the following is true: [Bailey starts with a certain amount of money. Bailey receives a weekly allowance of $8 for 8 weeks.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Bailey starts with a certain amount of money. Bailey receives a weekly allowance of $5 for 8 weeks.] At the end of 8 weeks, Bailey has a total of $100. If it is true that John is 45 miles from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by, then the following is true: [Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $10.] Otherwise, the following is true: [Eliza's rate per hour for the first 40 hours she works each week is $11.] Eliza also receives an overtime pay of 1.2 times her regular hourly rate. Eliza worked for 45 hours this week. John drives for 3 hours at a speed of 60 mph and then turns around because he realizes he forgot something very important at home. John tries to get home in 4 hours but spends the first 2 hours in standstill traffic.  John spends the next half-hour driving at a speed of 30mph, before being able to drive the remaining time of the 4 hours going at 80 mph. How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?", "solutions": [45, 460, 595, 60]}
{"id_chain": [92, 61, 45, 41, 64], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 200, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How old is Jackson?": 4}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [200, 104, 1430, 300, 4]}
{"id_chain": [11, 34, 29, 45, 61], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much did Toula have to pay in total?": 694, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [694, 104, 23, 104, 1430]}
{"id_chain": [35, 49, 32, 65, 72], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "How many hours does Jim spend on TV and reading in four weeks?": 36, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 221}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [35, 9, 30, 36, 221]}
{"id_chain": [88, 4, 29, 71, 82], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 60, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623, "How many copies did Harald sell?": 8000}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [20, 104, 60, 623, 8000]}
{"id_chain": [73, 1, 60, 45, 81], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 104, 17, 255, 17]}
{"id_chain": [82, 89, 64, 47, 68], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How much did Justin spend on ties?": 800, "How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?": 36}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [800, 300, 36, 623, 24]}
{"id_chain": [6, 82, 51, 4, 43], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 5, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [20, 260, 48, 5, 623]}
{"id_chain": [11, 60, 23, 48, 71], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much did Toula have to pay in total?": 694, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 60}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [694, 8, 8, 17, 60]}
{"id_chain": [88, 81, 45, 49, 24], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17, "How many copies did Harald sell?": 8000}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [26, 104, 30, 17, 8000]}
{"id_chain": [24, 39, 80, 22, 42], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10, "How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests?": 26}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [7, 26, 18, 26, 10]}
{"id_chain": [9, 71, 55, 89, 38], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "How fast does Jack run?": 10, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 60, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [460, 10, 14, 60, 24]}
{"id_chain": [61, 23, 52, 86, 45], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [8, 104, 15, 1430, 22]}
{"id_chain": [90, 11, 54, 41, 71], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much did Toula have to pay in total?": 694, "How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 200, "How many kittens does the Doubtfire family now have?": 40, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 60, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [694, 200, 40, 60, 225]}
{"id_chain": [3, 61, 55, 13, 88], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total meters does James run per week?": 540, "How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 18, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430, "How many copies did Harald sell?": 8000}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [540, 18, 14, 1430, 8000]}
{"id_chain": [76, 34, 16, 29, 48], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [230, 104, 23, 8, 5]}
{"id_chain": [52, 73, 9, 76, 28], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?": 25, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [460, 25, 15, 255, 5]}
{"id_chain": [90, 8, 16, 63, 61], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430, "Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.": 1596, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [45, 230, 1430, 1596, 225]}
{"id_chain": [81, 16, 18, 45, 44], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 7, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [230, 7, 20, 104, 17]}
{"id_chain": [29, 91, 39, 3, 37], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How many total meters does James run per week?": 360, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [540, 104, 2, 18, 28]}
{"id_chain": [69, 13, 59, 83, 33], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 18, "How many gold coins does Gretchen have?": 70, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": 187, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?": 600}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 70, 187, 60, 600]}
{"id_chain": [75, 39, 43, 88, 71], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 36, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 54, "What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60, "How many copies did Harald sell?": 4190}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 48, 60, 60, 8000]}
{"id_chain": [44, 34, 37, 22, 25], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [7, 2, 23, 2, 20]}
{"id_chain": [86, 26, 82, 25, 23], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [8, 2, 243, 623, 22]}
{"id_chain": [41, 39, 85, 22, 69], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 200, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 44, "How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [7, 18, 200, 60, 44]}
{"id_chain": [82, 51, 32, 88, 52], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 5, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623, "How many copies did Harald sell?": 8000}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [35, 5, 15, 623, 8000]}
{"id_chain": [39, 76, 81, 46, 42, 79], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 26, 163, 5, 70, 17]}
{"id_chain": [75, 58, 38, 72, 0, 48], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 10, 8, 57, 221, 60]}
{"id_chain": [65, 73, 75, 22, 54, 90], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [7, 40, 36, 255, 60, 225]}
{"id_chain": [82, 67, 50, 73, 88, 89], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [294, 595, 255, 623, 8000, 24]}
{"id_chain": [39, 38, 1, 37, 23, 6], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 4, "How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How fast does Jack run?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": "<UNKNOWN>"}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 260, 8, 2, 10, 18]}
{"id_chain": [85, 26, 79, 25, 73, 33], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "How many gold coins does Gretchen have?": 70, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 44}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [2, 243, 70, 255, 70, 44]}
{"id_chain": [55, 59, 34, 61, 52, 72], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": 167, "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 221}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [23, 15, 14, 187, 1430, 221]}
{"id_chain": [24, 67, 48, 28, 17, 6], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260, "What's Jill's annual salary?": 57500, "What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?": 25, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [260, 57500, 26, 25, 8, 595]}
{"id_chain": [88, 35, 61, 3, 18, 4], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total meters does James run per week?": 540, "How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 7, "How many total points did Mike score?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many copies did Harald sell?": "<UNKNOWN>"}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [540, 20, 7, 9, 1430, 8000]}
{"id_chain": [69, 26, 23, 47, 91, 49], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "How much did Justin spend on ties?": 800, "What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [8, 243, 800, 30, 60, 28]}
{"id_chain": [43, 48, 17, 46, 73, 72], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's Jill's annual salary?": 64500, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 36, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 173, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 12, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 307, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 306}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [57500, 48, 163, 8, 221, 255]}
{"id_chain": [92, 76, 32, 25, 39, 28], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?": 40, "How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5, "How old is Jackson?": 4}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [2, 25, 35, 18, 5, 4]}
{"id_chain": [13, 44, 71, 39, 38, 35], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 12, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How fast does Jack run?": 12, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 17, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 40, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 15}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 9, 10, 18, 20, 60]}
{"id_chain": [24, 10, 91, 81, 42, 41], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?": 366, "What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 200, "How many pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests?": 26, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [366, 26, 200, 26, 17, 28]}
{"id_chain": [49, 59, 73, 58, 24, 22], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 57, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": 187, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [7, 26, 30, 57, 187, 255]}
{"id_chain": [82, 26, 46, 22, 18, 0], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?": 26, "How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 7, "How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 7, 7, 243, 163, 623]}
{"id_chain": [35, 24, 29, 43, 0, 25], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?": 18, "What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 26, 2, 104, 9, 48]}
{"id_chain": [34, 79, 1, 80, 55, 83], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10, "How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?": 400}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 23, 14, 70, 10, 600]}
{"id_chain": [38, 76, 68, 72, 64, 37], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How fast does Jack run?": 10, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?": 36, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 221, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [2, 10, 300, 36, 221, 5]}
{"id_chain": [91, 58, 48, 60, 79, 39], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 57, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 8, 57, 17, 70, 28]}
{"id_chain": [86, 69, 35, 43, 29, 83], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?": 600, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [104, 9, 48, 60, 600, 22]}
{"id_chain": [90, 80, 26, 79, 85, 8], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 44, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [45, 243, 70, 10, 44, 225]}
{"id_chain": [28, 80, 61, 75, 35, 10], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?": 366, "How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?": 25, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430, "What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [366, 25, 9, 1430, 60, 10]}
{"id_chain": [23, 50, 92, 8, 10, 3], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total meters does James run per week?": 540, "How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": 45, "How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?": 366, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How old is Jackson?": 4}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [540, 45, 366, 8, 294, 4]}
{"id_chain": [25, 82, 29, 47, 86, 43], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48, "How much did Justin spend on ties?": 800, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [2, 104, 48, 800, 623, 22]}
{"id_chain": [46, 29, 9, 68, 4, 73, 50], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?": 36, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [20, 460, 104, 163, 294, 36, 255]}
{"id_chain": [41, 80, 72, 23, 55, 28, 25], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 12, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?": 40, "How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 100, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 16, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 307, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 6}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [8, 2, 25, 200, 14, 221, 10]}
{"id_chain": [6, 51, 52, 79, 72, 32, 9], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260, "How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 5, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 221, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [260, 460, 35, 5, 15, 221, 70]}
{"id_chain": [88, 64, 59, 45, 10, 75, 58], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?": "<UNKNOWN>", "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": "<UNKNOWN>", "After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 57, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": "<UNKNOWN>", "What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60, "How many copies did Harald sell?": "<UNKNOWN>"}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [366, 104, 57, 187, 300, 60, 8000]}
{"id_chain": [22, 79, 50, 25, 35, 42, 76], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many pieces of apple pie were taken by the guests?": 26, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [7, 2, 9, 26, 294, 5, 70]}
{"id_chain": [16, 47, 79, 29, 67, 75, 34], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "How much did Justin spend on ties?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": "<UNKNOWN>", "What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60, "How much does the grooming cost?": "<UNKNOWN>"}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [230, 104, 23, 800, 595, 60, 70]}
{"id_chain": [33, 54, 4, 82, 10, 35, 17], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many gold coins does Gretchen have?": 70, "How many kittens does the Doubtfire family now have?": 40, "How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623, "How many downloads did the new program have total over the three months?": 366, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "What's Jill's annual salary?": 57500}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [20, 366, 57500, 70, 9, 40, 623]}
{"id_chain": [89, 79, 92, 37, 91, 52, 1], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28, "How old is Jackson?": 4}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 2, 15, 70, 24, 28, 4]}
{"id_chain": [8, 18, 11, 85, 13, 46, 55], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How much did Toula have to pay in total?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": "<UNKNOWN>"}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [45, 694, 18, 7, 163, 14, 44]}
{"id_chain": [89, 50, 75, 46, 32, 51, 64], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 5, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [35, 163, 294, 5, 300, 60, 24]}
{"id_chain": [48, 35, 37, 54, 86, 64, 72], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How many kittens does the Doubtfire family now have?": 40, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 307, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [9, 2, 8, 40, 300, 221, 22]}
{"id_chain": [76, 16, 72, 83, 91, 79, 69], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 221, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70, "How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?": 600, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [230, 60, 221, 5, 70, 600, 28]}
{"id_chain": [55, 70, 0, 60, 59, 52, 38], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?": 18, "How fast does Jack run?": 10, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": 187, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17, "How much money does Judy make per week?": 7425}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 10, 15, 14, 187, 17, 7425]}
{"id_chain": [33, 54, 50, 37, 18, 24, 1], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 7, "What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "How many gold coins does Gretchen have?": 70, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How many kittens does the Doubtfire family now have?": 40}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 7, 26, 70, 2, 294, 40]}
{"id_chain": [39, 76, 4, 9, 1, 16, 46], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 7}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 20, 460, 230, 18, 163, 5]}
{"id_chain": [91, 61, 13, 73, 82, 80, 24], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 18, "What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "How much did Julia pay for the brooch in total?": 1430, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 26, 1430, 255, 10, 623, 28]}
{"id_chain": [69, 13, 4, 86, 23, 18, 67], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 18, "How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 7, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [20, 18, 7, 8, 595, 60, 22]}
{"id_chain": [1, 65, 82, 22, 25, 73, 76], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many hours does Jim spend on TV and reading in four weeks?": 36, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 7, 2, 36, 255, 5, 623]}
{"id_chain": [55, 46, 37, 67, 64, 33, 85], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many gold coins does Gretchen have?": 70, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 173, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How many miles can Sophia drive on a single tank of gas?": 300, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 595, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 48}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [70, 2, 163, 14, 300, 595, 44]}
{"id_chain": [51, 69, 67, 25, 70, 55, 4], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 3, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 30, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How many of the gems were there in the buried treasure chest?": 5, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 100, "How much money does Judy make per week?": 7425}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [20, 2, 5, 14, 595, 60, 7425]}
{"id_chain": [85, 3, 39, 6, 37, 76, 81], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total meters does James run per week?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many bags of dog food will Cecilia use in the first year?": 5, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": "<UNKNOWN>"}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [540, 260, 2, 18, 5, 17, 44]}
{"id_chain": [63, 26, 24, 43, 88, 90, 51], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"What was the original price of the book that Kyle bought?": 26, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 5, "Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.": 1596, "How many copies did Harald sell?": 8000, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [26, 243, 48, 5, 1596, 8000, 225]}
{"id_chain": [51, 25, 60, 43, 91, 48, 11], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much did Toula have to pay in total?": 694, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 48, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 5, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": 17, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [694, 2, 48, 8, 5, 17, 28]}
{"id_chain": [39, 44, 23, 91, 88, 35, 89], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 12, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 18, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 30, "How many copies did Harald sell?": 8000, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [8, 9, 18, 20, 8000, 24, 28]}
{"id_chain": [72, 35, 47, 83, 9, 68, 69], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 460, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How much did Justin spend on ties?": 800, "How many teachers are there in Dr Wertz's school?": 36, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How much money does Tommy raise?": 221, "How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?": 600}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [460, 9, 800, 36, 60, 221, 600]}
{"id_chain": [41, 17, 18, 59, 50, 3, 79, 69], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many total meters does James run per week?": 540, "What's Jill's annual salary?": 57500, "How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 7, "How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 200, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": 187, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [540, 57500, 7, 200, 294, 187, 60, 70]}
{"id_chain": [39, 4, 8, 60, 70, 48, 32, 83], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How many oranges in the basket are good?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How much money does Judy make per week?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many thorns are there total on all of Dan's roses?": 600}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [20, 45, 35, 18, 8, 17, 7425, 600]}
{"id_chain": [52, 59, 75, 69, 29, 1, 46, 51], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 5, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": 187, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 104, 163, 5, 15, 187, 60, 60]}
{"id_chain": [13, 52, 81, 16, 29, 38, 80, 32], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 18, "What's the distance covered by each of the two trains in the two days?": 230, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35, "How fast does Jack run?": 10, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 230, 104, 35, 10, 15, 10, 17]}
{"id_chain": [8, 35, 79, 43, 89, 0, 46, 1], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?": 14, "How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How far is John from home at the time he was originally trying to be home by?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many total points did Mike score?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "How much does the grooming cost?": "<UNKNOWN>", "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": "<UNKNOWN>"}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 3, 45, 9, 48, 163, 70, 24]}
{"id_chain": [32, 81, 23, 71, 44, 35, 37, 82], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 35, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 60, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [8, 35, 9, 2, 20, 60, 17, 623]}
{"id_chain": [18, 9, 73, 63, 58, 41, 80, 45], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 6, "How much are Eliza's earnings for this week?": 506, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 306, "Calculate the total amount Alena paid for the streaming service by the end of the year.": 1482, "After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 53, "How far outside of the reach of the dragon's flames could Polly stand and still hit the dragon with the gold javelin?": 0, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 6, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [460, 7, 200, 104, 57, 1596, 255, 10]}
{"id_chain": [65, 22, 38, 44, 50, 26, 23, 29], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many centimeters shorter will a candle be after burning from 1:00 PM to 5:00 PM?": 8, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "How many dollars are the boots that Gloria came across?": 104, "How fast does Jack run?": 10, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How many hours does Jim spend on TV and reading in four weeks?": 36}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [7, 8, 243, 104, 10, 20, 294, 36]}
{"id_chain": [85, 1, 82, 39, 32, 37, 34, 17], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 6, "What's Jill's annual salary?": 57500, "How many hours per week does Joseph spend taking care of dogs?": 42, "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 2, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 102, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 270, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 30}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 57500, 35, 23, 2, 18, 623, 44]}
{"id_chain": [17, 48, 52, 11, 44, 37, 75, 28], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much did Toula have to pay in total?": 694, "What's Jill's annual salary?": 57500, "How many miles did Henry travel between his first and second stops?": 25, "How many lego sets does Joshua still have?": 3, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How many toys does Uriah need to remove?": 15, "What is the average square footage of a level of the sandcastle?": 60}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [694, 57500, 25, 2, 20, 8, 15, 60]}
{"id_chain": [39, 71, 69, 49, 18, 6, 82, 26], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many sheep do Toulouse, Charleston, and Seattle have together?": 260, "How many dozens of eggs will Claire eat in four weeks?": 7, "How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "How many miles does Dana travel in six hours?": 36, "What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 36, "How many instructions does Kelian have to read to prepare the two dishes?": 54, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [260, 7, 243, 18, 30, 60, 60, 623]}
{"id_chain": [81, 0, 55, 48, 69, 89, 45, 86], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?": 18, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How many pieces of wire did Tracy obtain?": 8, "How many bags of lollipops can Jean fill?": 14, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How many stickers does Christopher have left?": 17, "How many times did Greg's alarm ring in all?": 22, "How much will Christina spend on gift bags?": 24}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 104, 8, 14, 60, 17, 22, 24]}
{"id_chain": [35, 51, 44, 91, 4, 25, 58, 34], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many cups of feed does Wendi need to give her chickens in the final meal of the day?": 20, "How many boxes of pizza did Marie order?": 2, "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20, "How long does it take Tom to get back?": 5, "After the extra fees, what was the final price of Stephen's groceries?": 57, "How many total pets do Jan, Marcia, and Cindy have total?": 28}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [20, 2, 23, 9, 20, 5, 57, 28]}
{"id_chain": [35, 59, 0, 80, 90, 82, 22, 73], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?": 18, "How many DVDs did Billy sell on Tuesday?": 7, "How many total points did Mike score?": 9, "How many raspberries does the raspberry bush have in total?": 187, "How much will Shiela pay per month for the cell phones?": 255, "How many liters of water were left after the two girls and the boy got water?": 10, "What is the combined weight of Grace and Alex in pounds?": 623, "How many pounds of potato salad does Ted need to bring to the picnic if he hopes to have enough to feed everyone?": 225}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [18, 7, 9, 187, 255, 10, 623, 225]}
{"id_chain": [50, 69, 1, 13, 44, 34, 43, 46], "is_correct": false, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many bolts of fiber in total does a robe take?": 3, "How many vacuum cleaners did Melanie start with?": 18, "How many jewels does Siobhan have?": 23, "How many grams of chips can you eat and not go over your daily calorie limit for today?": 36, "What is Charlie's net profit?": 20, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 173, "How much does Lloyd make on eggs per week?": 294, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [3, 18, 23, 48, 20, 163, 294, 60]}
{"id_chain": [46, 85, 65, 49, 79, 69, 45, 26], "is_correct": true, "model_string": "o1", "output": {"How many dollars did Mishka spend on all of the clothing items combined?": 243, "Calculate the total number of hours that Meredith spent writing articles in the three days.": 104, "How many Post-it notes were in the package that Candice purchased?": 163, "What's the total number of unoccupied units in Richard's apartment building?": 30, "How many hours does Jim spend on TV and reading in four weeks?": 36, "How much money did Bailey start with?": 60, "How much does the grooming cost?": 70, "How many quilt blocks does Gene have in total?": 44}, "problem": "Janet eats three eggs for breakfast every morning and bakes muffins for her friends every day with four eggs. Janet sells the remaining eggs at the farmers' market daily for $2 per fresh duck egg. How much in dollars does Janet make every day at the farmers' market?", "solutions": [243, 104, 163, 30, 36, 60, 70, 44]}